Where outlaws rule.
Apache Junction is a western, action, crime film directed by Justin Lee.
Apache Junction is an outpost of lawlessness, a haven
for thieves and cold-blooded killers.
After big-city reporter Annabelle Angel arrives to write an article on the town, she
becomes a target when notorious gunslinger Jericho Ford comes to her aid.
Now Annabelle must entrust her future to a man with a deadly
past, as Jericho heads toward a tense showdown.
Jericho Ford, played by Stuart Townsend.
Annabelle Angel, played by Scout Taylor-Compton.
Captain Hensley, played by Trace Adkins.
Al Longfellow, played by Thomas Jane.
Oslo Pike, played by Ed Morrone.
Christine Williams, played by Victoria Pratt.
Apache Junction is a 2021 Thai-American Western action adventure crime film written and directed by
Justin Lee and starring Stuart Townsend, Trace Adkins, Scout Taylor-Compton and Thomas Jane.
The tone is intense.